Guide to the Franz R. and Kathryn M. Stenzel Research Files on Western American Art
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Research Files for an Unpublished Book on Western Art, 1859-1997; Series V; 9.66; (23 boxes)
  - RESEARCH FILES
    - Artist Information Index
      - Main File
        - Brush - Bull, 1885-1965, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 307)
          Büchser, Frank
          Bull, W. H.
        - Burbank, E. A., 1900-65, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 308-309)
          Includes an article on Burbank in Truth
        - Burgess - Bushby, 1962-65, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 310)
          Burgess, George
          Burgdorff, Ferdinand
          Burr, Alfred
          Bush, Norton
          Bushby, Asa
        - Butler - Butman, 1963-68, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 311)
          Butler, Howard Russell
          Butler, John
          Butman, Frederick A.
        - Cadenasso - Carignano, 1964-65, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 312)
          Cadenasso, Giuseppe
          Camfferman, Margaret Gove
          Camfferman, Peter M.
          Campbell, A. P.
          Campbell, Hamilton
          Campion, Howard
          Cane, Henry
          Carey, Rockwell W.
          Carignano, Brother Joseph
        - Carpenter - Cary, 1958-74, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 313)
          Carpenter, Louise M.
          Carvalho, Solomon Nunes
          Cary, William de la Montagne
        - Casenelli - Caughey, 1897-1965, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 314)
          Casenelli, Victor
          Catherwood, Frederick
          Catlin, George
          Caughey, Rollin B.
          Includes letter to R. Caughey from
          Sister M. Bernadine, from the
          College Notre Dame, San Jose, dated
          1897 Apr 1
        - Challoner - Christmas, 1961-75, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 315)
          Challoner, William Lindsey
          Champness, W.
          Chancellor, H.
          Chapman, O. F.
          Chase, Albert
          Chittenden, Alice Brown
          Christmas, E. W.
        - Clark - Cogswell, 1948-72, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 316)
          Clark, Hobart
          Clark, Jennie
          Clarke, Frank C.
          Clausen, Peter Gui
          Cogswell, William F.
        - Coleman, Edmund Thomas - Coleman, Samuel, 1906-63, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 317)
          Includes Vol. 1, No. 1 of Steel Points, published by William
          Gladstone Steel, 1906
        - Collins, Caspar W. - Colman, Samuel, 1954-63, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 318)
          Includes An Army Wife Comes West. Letters of Catharine Wever Collins, edited by Agnes Wright
          Spring, 1954
          folder 1576
        - Colyer - Cooper, Astley David, 1961-72, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 319)
          Colyer, Vincent
          Comparet, Alexis
          Cook, Clyde Benton
          Cooper, Astley David
        - Cooper, Frederick G. - Coughlin, 1938-65, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 320)
          Cooper, Frederick G.
          Cooper, James G.
          Corbett, Fred
          Corwin, Charles Abel
          Coughlin, A. T.
        - Coulter, William Alexander, 1922-67, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 321)
        - Couse, Eanger Irving - Covington, Richard, 1957-68, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 322)
        - Cox - Craig, 1943-72, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 323)
          Cox, Charles Brinton
          Cozzens, Frederick
          Craig, Charles
        - Cram - Cross, 1935-65, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 324)
          Cram, Leo D.
          Crawford, Will
          Crayon, Porte
          Crocker, Sally S.
          Cronau, Rudolph Daniel
          Cronyn, George W.
          Cross, Osborne
          Cross, Henry H.
        - Curtis - Davenport, 1959-74, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 325)
          Curtis, Herbert
          Dana, James Dwight
          Darley, Felix Octavius Carr
          Davenport, Homer Calvin
          Davenport, T. R.
          Davenport, W. H.
        - Davidson - Deakin, 1962-65, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 326)
          Davidson, George
          Davies, Arthur Bowen
          Davis, Leonard M.
          Davis, Theodore Russell
          Davis, Willis
          Deakin, Edwin
        - DeCamp, Ralph - DeGirardin, E., 1957-68, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 327)
        - Dellenbaugh, Frederick Samuel - Deming, Edwin Willard, 1913-66, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 328)
          Includes an illustrated card signed
          by Deming dated 1913
        - Denny - De Yong, 1963-67, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 329)
          Denny, E. I.
          Derby, George Horatio
          de Thulstrup, Thure
          DeTrobriand, Phillippe Regis
          De Yong, Joe
        - Dixon - Downing, 1911-68, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 330)
          Dixon, Maynard Lafayette
          Dodge, Grenville Mellen
          Dowd, Delia
          Dowling, Colista
          Downing, Alfred A.
          folder 1603
        - Drayton - Durkin, 1914-68, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 331)
          Drayton, Joseph
          Duncan, Johnson Kelly
          Dunton, William Herbert
          Durkin, John
          Includes Winter Camp Dinner, The
          Camp-Fire Club of America menu
          from Delmonico's, Jan 9 1914
        - Eastman - Edwards, 1963-72, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 332)
          Eastman, Harrison
          Eastman, Seth
          Eaton, Joseph Horace
          Eaton, Charles Warren
          Edwards, [----?]
        - Eggenhofer, Nick, 1950-74, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 333)
        - Eisele - Emmons, 1962-77, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 334)
          Eisele, Christian
          Elkins, Henry Arthur
          Elliott, Henry Wood
          Elwell, Robert Farrington
          Emmons, George Foster
        - Engel - Evans, 1962-72, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 335)
          Engel, Paul Max
          Engelhart, J. Jacob
          Epting, Henry H.
          Espey, Edward
          Euwer, Anthony
          Evans, M. E.
          folder 1577
        - Fairbanks, J. Leo - Farnsworth, Alfred, 1963-65, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 336)
        - Farny, Henry F., 1954-64, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 337)
        - Farthingberg - Ferry, 1951-64, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 338)
          Farthingberg, J.
          Fenn, Harry
          Ferry, Clinton Peyre
        - Fery, John, 1960-74, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 339)
        - Fichet - Frenzeny, 1908-73, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 340)
          Fichet, C. O.
          Fife, William
          Fisk, Lizzie
          Fisken, Jessie
          Fitler, William Crothers
          Foote, A. Freeman
          Foote, Mary Hallock
          Fountain, Grace
          Frenzeny, Paul
        - Friend - Furlong, 1949-67, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 341)
          Friend, Washington
          Frost, George Albert
          Frush, William H.
          Fulton, Cyrus James
          Furlong, Charles Wellington
        - Gale - Garrigan, 1961-65, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 342)
          Gale, Goddard
          Garner, Clarence Leander
          Garrigan, John H.
          folder 1604
        - Gass - Gay, 1893-1965, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 343)
          Gass, Patrick
          Gaul, William Gilbert
          Gay, George Howell
          Includes an article on Gilbert Gaul
          entitled "An American Military
          Artist" by George Parsons Lathrop
          from The Quarterly Illustrator Vol. I, No. 4 October, November,
          and December, 1893
          folder 1578
        - Gegoux, Theodore, 1963-73, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 344-345)
        - Geyer, Charles Andrew - Gibbs, George (Box 17, Folder 346)
        - Gifford, Robert Swain, 1874-1966, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 347)
          folder 1605
        - Gifford, Sanford Robinson, 1963-74, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 348)
          folder 1579
        - Gilbert - Gilder, 1928-76, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 349)
          Gilbert, Romeo Monroe
          Gilder, Robert Fletcher
          Gilder, William H.
        - Gillespie - Gloster, 1962-68, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 350)
          Gillespie, Robert L.
          Gilstrap, William Henry
          Gleason, Joe Duncan
          Gloster, Charles A.
        - Gollings, Elling William, 1906-63, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 351)
          Includes letters from Hans Kleiber
          to Stenzel about Gollings,
          "Autobiography of Elling William
          Gollings, Cowboy Artist" in Annals of Wyoming Vol. 9, No. 2, October
          1932, postcards of Gollings' art,
          and a February, 1906 cover of The Pacific Monthly
        - Goodwin - Gookins, 1963-75, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 352)
          Goodwin, Philip R.
          Goodwin, Richard La Barre
          Gookins, James Farrington
        - Gordon - Graham, 1963-65, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 353)
          Gordon, Charles S.
          Gorham, Aimee Spencer
          Grafström, Olaf Jonas
          Graham, Charles
          Graham, Robert Alexander
        - Granger - Green, 1913-71, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 354)
          Granger, Caroline Gibbons
          Gray, Percy
          Gray, U. L.
          Green, Emma Edwards
          Green, Mary
          Includes photographs of Percy Gray
          and his studio
        - Greene - Grinnell, 1957-74, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 355)
          Greene, LeRoy E.
          Grigware, Edward Thomas
          Grinnell, George Bird
        - Griset, Ernest Henry, 1964, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 356)
          Stored also in: Oversize box 57,
          folder 1580
        - Grob - Gustin, 1916-64, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 357)
          Grob, Trautman
          Groll, Albert Lorey
          Grothjean, Francesca C. R.
          Grover, John Culver
          Guillou, Charles F. B.
          Gustin, Paul Morgan
          Includes: Bulletin of the Seattle Fine Arts Society. Exhibition of Paintings by Paul Morgan Gustin,
          1920, signed by Gustin
          folder 1581
        - Habersham - Handforth, 1963-79, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 358)
          Habersham, R. P.
          Hagerup, Nels
          Hall, Bob
          Hall, Cyrrinus
          Hall, J. B.
          Hamilton, James
          Hamilton, L. A.
          Hammerstrow, H.
          Handforth, Thomas Schofield
          Includes signed photograph of Bob
          Hall, an undated letter from Bob
          Hall, and three postcards to Bob
          Hall
        - Hansen - Harwood, 1929-64, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 359)
          Hansen, Hermann W.
          Hanson, J.
          Hardwick, Lily Norling
          Harley, Steve
          Harmer, Thomas C.
          Harmon, Annie L.
          Harrison, Alexander
          Hart, Lance
          Harwood, James T.
        - Haseltine - Hays, 1959-69, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 360)
          Haseltine, William Stanley
          Hassam, Childe
          Hatch, C. E.
          Hauser, John
          Hauser, Samuel Thomas
          Hayes, Lee
          Hayes, William Patrick
          Hays, William J.
        - Hazeltine - Heidelman, 1925-75, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 361)
          Hazeltine, Amy Wood
          Heade, Martin Johnson
          Heaney, Charles Edward
          Heath, Frank L.
          Heger, Anthony
          Heidelman, Elizabeth
        - Hencke - Henri, 1936-66, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 362)
          Hencke, Albert
          Henckel, Carl
          Henderson, William Penhallow
          Henri, Robert
        - Heuston, George Zell - Heywood, Herbert, 1908-64, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 363)
        - Hill, Abby - Hill, John Henry, 1958-77, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 364)
          Hill, Abby
          Hill, Edward Rufus
          Hill, Evelyn Corthell
          Hill, John Henry
        - Hill, Thomas, 1962-72, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 365)
        - Hitchins - Holmes, Ralph, 1958-74, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 366)
          Hitchins, Joseph
          Hoffman, Frank Butler
          Holdredge, Ransom Gillet
          Holland, G. M.
          Holliday, Robert
          Holmes, Fred Mason
          Holmes, Ralph
        - Holmes, William Henry - Horsky, 1933-65, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 367)
          Holmes, William Henry
          Holt, Henry
          Holtes, Charles
          Hopper, Edward
          Horsfall, Robert Bruce
          Horsky, Emery Donaldson
        - Houghton - Howe, Frank Maynard, 1926-64, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 368)
          Houghton, Merritt Dana
          Houlahan, Kathleen
          House, Howard Elmer
          Howe, Frank Maynard
        - Howe, Henry - Howland, John Dare, 1951-64, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 369)
          folder 1582
        - Hudson - Hutton, 1963-73, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 370)
          Hudson, Charles Bradford
          Hudson, Lillian
          Huntington, Daniel Riggs
          Hutchings, James Mason
          Hutton, James
        - Inchbold - Isaacs, 1950-65, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 371)
          Inchbold, Stanley
          [Inschoot, ----?]
          Irwin, Rea
          Isaacs, Walter F.
          folder 1583
        - Jackson - Jacobsen, 1940-65, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 372)
          Jackson, William Franklin
          Jackson, William Henry
          Jacobi, Otto Reinhard
          Jacobsen, Antonio
        - James - Johanson, 1961-75, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 373)
          James, Mary
          James, Will
          James, Elsa
          Jennings, Oliver
          Johansen, Eric
        - Johnson, David - Johnson, Frank, 1938-75, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 374)
          Johnson, David
          Johnson, Eastman
          Johnson, Frank Tenney
        - Johnson, George Cady - Juke, 1906-69, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 375)
          Johnson, George Cady
          Johnson, Joseph Hoffman
          Joliet, Auguste
          Jones, [----?]
          Jonnevold, Christian
          Joullin, Amadee
          Judson, William Lees
          Juke, [----?]
          folder 1584
        - Jump - Kane, 1968-71, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 376)
          Jump, Edward
          Junk, Anna M.
          Kalling, G.
          Kane, Paul
        - Kapp - Kern, 1971, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 377)
          Kapp, Frank
          Kehoe, Joseph William
          Keith, William
          Keller, Arthur Ignatius
          Keller, Clyde Leon
          Kemble, Edward Windsor
          Kensett, John Frederick
          Kern, Edward Meyer
          Includes a letter to Stenzel from
          W. Averell Harriman 1971 Oct 8
        - Kerns - Kilpatrick, 1964-72, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 378)
          Kerns, Maude Irvine
          Kihn, William Langdon
          Kilpatrick, Aaron Edward
        - Kleiber, Hans, 1961-71, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 379)
          Includes typescript photocopy of
          "A Biographical Foreward" by Hans
          Kleiber, and photographs of Kleiber
          Related Archival Materials note
          See also: Gollings, Elling William, box 17, folder 351
        - Knowles, Joe, 1911-64, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 380-381)
          Includes Knowles' Participant's
          permit for the Panama-Pacific
          International Exposition, San
          Francisco, 1915 with photograph
          inside; a letter to "Howard" from
          Joe Knowles dated 1937 Mar 24; a
          letter from Charles E. L. Wingate,
          Sunday Editor of the Boston Post to
          W. T. Stott of The Portland Oregon
          concerning Knowles, dated 1919
          Apr 9; and Winter Camp Dinner, The
          from Delmonico's, Jan 9 1914, an
          advertisement for an appearance by
          Joe Knowles, "The Nature Man"
        - Koerner, William Henry Dethlef, 1963-75, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 382)
        - Kohler - Lamade, 1964-73, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 383)
          Kohler, Carl
          Kollock, Mary
          Krieghoff, William G.
          Kurtz, Rudolph F.
          Lakes, Arthur
          Lamade, Erich
        - Lambourne - Laurence, 1962-70, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 384)
          Lambourne, Alfred
          Laray, Emil
          Larsen, Benjamin D.
          Laurence, Sydney
        - Lauritz - Leighton, 1955-63, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 385)
          Lauritz, Paul
          Lawrence, J. F.
          Lee, Bertha Stringes
          Leigh, William Robinson
          Leighton, Kathryn Woodman
        - Lenders - Lindneux, 1923-74, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 386)
          Lenders, Emil
          Leonard, Nathan Frank "Bud"
          Lillywhite, Richard
          Lillywhite, Ilka Benko
          Lindneux, Robert Ottokar
          Includes photograph of Raphael
          Lillywhite painting in his studio
        - Lindsay - Lofgren, 1956-64, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 387)
          Lindsay, Andrew Jackson
          Lindsay, Thomas Corwin
          Livermore, Grace C.
          Lochrie, Elizabeth Tangye Davey
          Lofgren, A. Charles
          folder 1585
        - Logan - Lungren, 1957-65, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 388)
          Logan, Maurice
          Lomans, A. F.
          Loomis, Pasqual
          Lorenz, Richard
          Lowther, Mabel Russell
          Lungren, Ferdinand Harvey
          Includes Maurice Logan's letter of
          election to the National Academy of
          Design, 1960 Mar 3
        - Machetanz - Maltby, 1930-64, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 389)
          Machetanz, Fred
          Magelssen, Nell Buretti
          Mallory, G. B.
          Maltby, Elizabeth
        - Manser - Martinez, 1903-73, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 390)
          Manser, Percy L.
          Marchand, John Norval
          Marks, Alfred Edwin
          Marple, WIlliam Lewis
          Martin, Jo G.
          Martinez, Peter Paul
        - Masterson - Matthews, 1963-77, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 391)
          Masterson, James W.
          Mathews, Alfred E.
          Matthews, W. D.
          folder 1586
        - McBain - McIlwraith, 1888-1964, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 392)
          McBain, Robert Ventress
          McComas, E. S.
          McCormack, Adeline Willoughby
          McEntee, Jervis
          McIlwraith, William Forsyth
          Includes printed catalogs of works
          by Jervis McEntee and a printed
          pamphlet about him
        - McMeekin, Joseph Patrick - McMicken, Helen Parker, 1960-72, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 393)
        - McMurtrie, William Birch, 1959-74, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 394-395)
        - Meakin - Mersfelder, 1963-67, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 396)
          Meakin, Lewis Henry
          Melrose, Andrew
          Mersfelder, Jules
        - Metcalf - Meyer, 1882-1965, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 397)
          Metcalf, Willard Leroy
          Mettman, William
          Meyer, Richard Max
          Includes photographs of Richard Max
          Meyer's studio in Tacoma and his
          painting of Mount Tacoma as
          published by Wagenss Photo in
          Tacoma, two calling cards, and
          several documents belonging to
          Richard Max Meyer
        - Meyers - Mills, 1957-74, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 398)
          Meyers, S. E. B.
          Miller, Alfred Jacob
          Miller, Evylena Nunn
          Milleson, Royal Hill
          Mills, John Harrison
          folder 1587
        - Moellman - Moore, 1963-70, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 399)
          Moellman, Charles Frederick
          Möllhausen, Heinrich Balduin
          Moor, E. N.
          Moore, M. H.
          folder 1588
        - Moran - Mulvany, 1900-72, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 400)
          Moran, Peter
          Moran, Thomas
          Morrison, Nelson John
          Moser, Henri
          Muir, John
          Mulvany, John
        - Munger - Nash, 1964-80, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 401)
          Munger, Gilbert Davis
          Nahl, Charles Christian
          Nash, Louisa A'Huenty
          Nash, Wallis
        - Nicholl, Thomas Jeff - Nielson, T. R., 1899-1965, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 402)
        - Norling - Ostner, 1939-63, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 403)
          Norling, Ernest Ralph
          Northern, Ellen Gifford
          Ormson, Bogi Holm
          O'Ryan, Lillia
          Ostner, Charles
        - Ottinger, George Martin - Palenske, Reinhold H., 1881-1965, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 404)
          folder 1606
        - Parrott - Pattie, 1963-72, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 405)
          Parrott, William Samuel
          Parrott, Sue
          Partridge, Roi
          Patterson, Ambrose
          Pattie, James Ohio
        - Paxson, E. S., 1902-67, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 406-407)
          folder 1607
          Includes A Portfolio of The Art of E. S. Paxson. Montana
          Historical Society Press and
          Montana Magazine of History,
          Spring 1954 issue, and Merchant Princes of the Plains by Paul F.
          Sharp. Montana Historical Society
          Press, Montana Heritage Series
          No. 5
        - Peale, Titian Ramsay, 1964, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 408)
        - Pease, Lute, 1897-1963, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 409-410)
          Includes photographs of Lute Pease
          March, April and October 1907,
          December 1908, April 1911 cover by
          Pease of The Pacific Monthly, the
          July 1911 cover of The Pacific Monthly by C.E.S. Wood; stationery
          for The Pacific Monthly with Lute
          Pease, editor letterhead; campaign
          card for "Lute Pease Progressive
          Nominee for County Commissioner"
        - Pease, Nell - Phillips, 1957-75, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 411)
          Pease, Nell
          Pebbles, Frank Marion
          Pennell, Joseph
          Pennoyer, Albert Sheldon
          Perard, Victor
          Perret, Ferdinand
          Peters, Charles Rollo
          Petit, Dale
          Pettis, M. F.
          Phelps, Thomas Stowell
          Phillips, Walter Shelley
          Includes illustrated memorial
          exhibition catalog of A. Sheldon
          Pennoyer artworks, 1958
        - Pickett - Plowman, 1962-75, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 412)
          Pickett, James Tilton
          Piercy, Frederick
          Plowman, George Taylor
        - Point, Nicholas, 1959-66, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 413)
        - Pond - Potthast, 1900-74, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 414)
          Pond, Elizabeth Parrott
          Pond, Sue Hendershott
          Poor, Henry Vaughan
          Poore, Henry R.
          Pope, Franklin L.
          Potthast, Edward Henry
          Includes an article on Edward H.
          Potthast in December 1900 issue of Truth
        - Powell - Preuss, 1963-77, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 415)
          Powell, "Ace"
          Powell, Arthur James Emery
          Powell, Lucien Whiting
          Preuss, Charles
        - Price - Puthuff, 1910-65, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 416)
          Price, Clayton S.
          Purves, C.
          Puthuff, Hanson Duvall
          Includes illustrated retrospective
          exhibition catalog by the Portland
          Art Museum, 1942; The Pacific Monthly cover for March 1910 by
          Price and various illustrations for
          Pacific Monthly by Price; and two
          postcards of work by Price
        - Quigley, Edward B., 1936-71, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 417-418)
          Includes Quigley covers for Western
          Horseman, September 1953, Western
          Livestock Journal cover for August
          1963; a Christmas card designed by
          Quigley, signed "Quig"
        - Quinlan - Ralston, 1960-65, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 419)
          Quinlan, William J.
          Rabjohn, J.
          Raborg, Benjamin
          Raleigh, Henry P.
          Ralston, James Kenneth
        - Ranney, William Tylee, 1961-79, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 420)
          1589
        - Ravalli - Reinhart, 1963-65, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 421)
          Ravalli, Anthony
          Redwood, Allen Christian
          Reed, Cyrus A.
          Reinhart, Charles Stanley
          folder 1590
        - Reiss - Richardson, 1898-1972, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 422)
          Reiss, Winold
          Remington, Frederic
          Rich, William
          Richard, William Trost
          Richardson, Theodore J.
          Includes a letter from Frederic
          Remington to Mr. Harper dated May
          20 1898; "A Bunch of Buckskins" by
          Owen Wister, illustrated by
          Frederic Remington from The Metropolitan Magazine June 1906
          issue
        - Richter - Rix, 1906-67, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 423)
          Richter, Henry L.
          Riesenberg, Sidney H.
          Riess, William J.
          Riley, G. B.
          Rix, Julian Walbridge
          Includes Sidney H. Riesenberg's